the world is conspiring against me a
little bit this morning I got up to get
my daughter to the bus made myself a
coffee in my to go contain in my thermos
and managed to spill it in my car while
this steam was coming up where's that
coming from
at least now my car is gonna smell
lovely of coffee for the next while
because I don't even know how to clean
it up it's like under the seat and then
on the way home like I'll treat myself
to a coffee there was parking spots but
I had already passed them so I pulled up
a couple blocks and walked back to one
of the coffee shops and it's closed to
close down like two months ago which I
figured out right before I got there
like at the crosswalk to go up to go
across the street and then my grocery
shopping they don't have coffee grinders
there so I can buy the coffee in bulk
but I can't grind it I do have a bit of
coffee left so I'm going to go and you
have that right after because I don't so
much need it for the mornings like I
mean I'm awake it's ten o'clock I don't
need it to wake up but I do need it
because I had a caffeine headache in the
afternoon late afternoon if I haven't
had coffee yet I did manage to go out
off of coffee a few months ago and dealt
with the headaches and the bitchiness
for days and then somehow I went back on
coffee cuz it's delicious
so I kind of have to either pick either
completely off or completely on and I
guess I could have decaf coffee but
what's the point in that
do you cup coffee stay off of it no such
as that odd morning where I do really
need a pick-me-up the next anti cup of
coffee
I'm just a morning person if I could
have coffee in the afternoon maybe I
could function but yeah that was my mind
a plus I got I noticed I've been off of
off on disability and not being able to
work full time I paid my bills up until
like the last month I wasn't able to and
then food and shelter became a priority
so I stopped paying my credit card bills
as I would suggest everyone to do and I
just find the creditor so weird I mean
this was three and a half years ago that
I
jobs pain and I had like 20,000 and
credit card debt between over the course
of years and I was paying the bare
minimum which is not what you want to do
but yeah and now the one I don't know it
must be that credit card cuz they're
like you owe 30 thousands it's about
increased ten thousand which I guess
happens you know pay for three and half
years but they sent me this letter which
was more or less like give us the thirty
thousand we've made this installment
plan of five thousand dollars per month
for you and if you pay it there'll be no
legal action but if you don't pay it not
only will you have to cover this cost
but you'll have to also cover the legal
action cost and okay yeah you've got you
go ahead you take a single mom on
disability to court you see how much
money the courts are gonna give you I
don't have money like you can't get
blood from a stone so if I don't have
this thirty thousand and haven't paid
any or twenty thousand it's now thirty
thousand and you and I haven't paid
anything on it in three and half years
do you think I have five thousand
dollars a month like who has five
thousand dollars a month just makes me
laugh and it's like it's been
transferred so many times there's so
many different people it's like well the
money you owe to these people who is
that do you even know why are you it's
like I was gonna pay it off I would go
through one of the collected the people
who you can pay like half a bit or a
quarter of it I definitely wouldn't be
paying you mr. lawyer the full amount in
five thousand dollar installments I have
to call Telus this morning because I got
a bill from from them it's been I'm very
blessed to get internet high speed
internet for ten dollars a month because
I Momo on disability and they gave out
like a few thousand vouchers for ten
dollars for a year and I signed up and
then I got a call in the in the spring
saying we're gonna increase it another
year which is awesome so I have it to
like March of 2019 $10 a month Internet
honey so but then they called a few
months ago and they're like oh we're
doing like high fiber optics in your
neighborhood it won't cost you anything
in fact early better and we'll jet
I'm like but I'm on this $10 a month fun
they're like yeah I still have that like
okay so I signed up for it I just got my
bill I before I switched over to this
$10 a month one I just paid this I
hadn't paid it for a few months and so I
ended up paying like $200 but it ended
up double pain so I 200 all are sitting
on there so I haven't paid it in forever
because it's ten dollars that's like 20
months worth of payments and so this
time comes and it's like I had to think
80 bucks left on it and it's like
charging me 70 which means it's charging
me like a hundred and fifty dollars for
Internet who pays a hundred and fifty
dollars for Internet anyway I'm sorry
even if it's top of the line that's
ridiculous
for just internet and on cable not phone
not anything else on top of it anyway so
I'm - phone that many be like okay so
you guys need to switch me back to the
other one or like what did you do and I
asked her I didn't know how many times I
was on it like yes but I got this $10
one $10 one right so that was my morning
opening the mail it's only Monday today
I didn't do my one err I did one extra
video in the weekend so this is video
number 25 I'm gonna try to catch up that
may be due to date to today but my mail
got tell us bill was expecting alert but
from a lawyer
BAM I saw some coffee to bring my child
to school spilt in the car the other
ones clothes it's like one of those days
you guys just go back to bed
how many coffee yet I could write but
it's also just the universe playing
pranks because none of them none of it's
horrible none of its gonna mean the
difference of a roof over my head
unless lawyer does have teeth and come
after me for literally the roof over my
head like if you can come after me for
my disability money yeah they don't have
a problem negative negative five
thousand dollars a month in but yeah I
think I know too much for them to
believe me
I know what you went for the legal
system I used to work in a bank I know
yeah I know enough to know that they can
unclutch made everything call they pay a
robot to call me like I'm never calling
back a robot pay a human being to call
me and I'll explain the situation I did
when I first started not being able to
pay back I called all the creditors in
explain if they didn't pass that
information on when they sold my debt
sorry not sorry you can figure it out
some other way yeah that's my morning
hope you're having a better morning than
me I'm gonna go find some coffee